Guide to the Lois Milner collection of broadcast radio audio recordings 1940-1952
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
Lois Milner collection of broadcast radio audio recordings
1940-1952
University of Utah Libraries, Special Collections Audio Visual Archives Special Collections 295 South 1500 East Salt Lake City, Utah 84112-0860 801-581-8864 http://www.lib.utah.edu/collections/multimedia-archives/
A1005
Milner, Lois
250 phonograph records, 135 compact discs.
The Lois Lois Milner collection of broadcast radio audio recordings contains 259 phonograph records of radio programs from 1940-1952. These programs cover a variety of topics but appear to mostly be targeted towards children, or related to school in some way.
Historical Note
In 1895, Marconi had the first succesful long distance radio transmission, spanning approximately 1.5 miles. As technology allowed radio to become a better communication and entertainment medium, it grew rapidly. By the 1940s, most households had a receiver and many commercially produced shows were available. Adaptations of written works, such as the "Children's Friend of the Air" programs in the Lois Lois Milner collection of broadcast radio audio recordings were common as well.
The Lois Lois Milner collection of broadcast radio audio recordings contains 135 cds of radio programs from 1940-1952. These programs cover a variety of topics but appear to mostly be targeted towards children, or related to school in some way. All records have been digitized and are available to listen to on the 135 compact discs detailed in this finding aid.
Materials are arranged in the order in which they were digitized.
Materials must be used on-site; no use of original material, access copies will be made available for viewing. Five business days advanced notice required. Access to parts of this collection may be restricted under provisions of state or federal law, condition of the material, or by donor.
Donated by Lois Milner in 2009.
Radio; Children's radio programs; Social Life and Customs; Sound Recordings; Sound recordings
- Milner Discs, 1940-1952
  - 1949 February-1949 March, Compact disc (Disc 1)
    - "Sweet Music in a Dreary World," Children's Friend of the Air (not finished due to damage), Children's Friend - The Elephants Friend, 1949 February 26; 1949 February 19 (Track 1)
    - Children's Friend - Keeper of the Draw – Sandra Sarri, Children's Friend of the Air – Exchange with Rosita, 1949 March 19; 1949 March 26 (Track 2)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Wash Out", Children's Friend - Gar Fish For Supper, 1949 March 5; 1949 March 12 (Track 3)
  - 1949 February-1949 July, Compact disc (Disc 2)
    - Children's Friend - Willie Wind, Children's Friend "A Place For Everything + Everything in it's Place", 1949 April 9; 1949 April 2 (Track 4)
    - Children's Friend "Skating is Fun in Any Language", Swing Time 2, 1949 February 12; 1949 July 27 (Track 5)
  - 1947 January-1948 December, Compact disc (Disc 3)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Free Supper", 4009B, 1948 December 25; 1948 December 14 (Track 6)
    - *Children's Friend of the Air - Easter Bunny – Hobbs, 1862-B (unrecordable due to bad condition), 1947 April 5 (Track 7)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Children of Mt. Vernon" Holby: Howard Allen Children (Damaged), Children's Friend of the Air "The Tale of Too Bad" Hobbs, 1947 February 22; 1947 January 25 (Track 8)
  - 1947 December-1949 February, Compact disc (Disc 4)
    - Children's Friend – Coalies New Year's Wish – Hobbs (End Damaged), Children's Friend – Xmas Songs of Grandma 1 (Can't Record), 1947 December 27; 1947 December 20 (Track 9)
    - Children's Friend – The Red Book in the Dusty Road, Children's Friend "Humpy the Camel Finds His Own Pyramid", 1949 January 22; 1949 January 29 (Track 10)
    - Children's Friend – The Selfish Prince – Hobbs, Children's Friend of the Air – Thomas Edisons Adventure, 1949 January 8; 1949 February 5 (Track 11)
  - 1947 June-1950 November, Compact disc (Disc 5)
    - MC Caramel 2,Children's Friend - Birthday Record – Holby Part 2 – "Mopey" (End Damaged), 1947 June 14; 1947 June 14-19 (Track 12)
    - Children's Friend – Mopey – Birthday Record 1 – ½ hr. Show (Heavily Damaged, Couldn't Record), Children's Friend – Patricia's Wish and What Happened, 1947 June 14; 1947 June 7 (Track 13)
    - Children's Friend "Bimpy Butterfly", Who Said That? II, 1948 July 10; 1948 July 9 (Track 14)
    - P.T.A. "This is Your P.T.A." What Teachers Like in a Parent 2, 1950 November 27 (Track 15)
  - 1947 December-1949 February, Compact disc (Disc 6)
    - P.T.A. "This is Your P.T.A." What Teachers Like in a Parent 2, 1950 November 27 (Track 15)
    - This is Your P.T.A. – P.T.A. Meeting, Watch Your Longwide Part 2, 1950 November 20; 1950 December 10 (Track 16)
    - Children's Friend – Kanga-Goo, Children's Friend – The Last Page (Snowstorm), 1948 December 11; 1948 December 4 (Track 17)
  - 1947 March-1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 7)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Skipper Salutes the Flag, Children's Friend – Redskin Ransom – Hobbs, 1948 June 28; 1947 March 1 (Track 18)
    - Children's Friend – Mr. Seen Goes on Strike, Children's Friend – Holby the Horse Goes Gallops, 1948 April 24; 1948 May 15 (Track 19)
    - Children's Friend – Sailor in the Mountains, Children's Friend – 2nd Birthday Part I – Guests no drama, 1948 June 5; 1948 June 12 (Track 20)
  - 1947 November-1958 July, Compact disc (Disc 8)
    - Children's Friend – Sailor in the Mountains, Children's Friend – 2nd Birthday Part I – Guests no drama, 1948 June 5; 1948 June 12 (Track 20)
    - Treasury Department Radio Recording – "Guest Star" Benny Goodman and his Orchestra with Del Sharbutt, Treasury Department Radio Recording – "Guest Star" Anna Maria Alberghetti with John Cante' and Basil Adlam and His Orchestra, 1958 July 6; 1958 April 27 (Track 21)
    - Children's Friend – Prissella Finds Her Place, Can You Top This? Part II, 1947 November 15; 1947 November 14 (Track 22)
  - 1946 December-1948 July, Compact disc (Disc 9)
    - Children's Friend – Hobbs – Three Wishes Xmas Doll, Children's Friend of the Air – Saint Nicholas Porridge, 1946 December 14; 1946 December 7 (Track 23)
    - DUP Pioneer Village Sonoma Inn, 19?? November 10 (Track 24)
    - Narration by Ken Linn Kuta, Undated (Track 25)
    - Pioneer Village – Pie Near Village, Undated (Track 26)
    - New Record, Undated (Track 27)
    - Penny Appeal (Quartet) Theme, Undated (Track 28)
    - DUP Pioneer Village, Undated (Track 29)
    - DUP Pioneer Village, Undated (Track 30)
    - DUP Pioneer Village Master, 1948 July 15 (Track 31)
  - 1946 August-1948 July, Compact disc (Disc 10)
    - DUP Pioneer Village Master, 1948 July 15 (Track 31)
    - DUP Pioneer Village, Undated (Track 32)
    - DUP Pioneer Village, Undated (Track 33)
    - The State 7 Log, America's 1 Farmer, 1947 January 12; 1947 January 11 (Track 34)
    - Heartthrobs of the West – Carson Mission, 1946 August 25 (Track 35)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Mt. Timpanogos, Heiser Spots (Can't record), 1947 May 16; 1947 June 1 (Track 36)
  - 1946 August-1947 June, Compact disc (Disc 11)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Pioneer Courtships 2 1/2, 1947 May 2 (Track 37)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Ellis Reynolds Ship – Woman Doctor, 1947 April 5 (Track 38)
    - Heart Throbs – A Ship to S.J. (Skips), 1946 August 11 (Track 39)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Heber C Kimball, Funny Paper Part II, 1947 June 27 (Track 40)
  - 1945 June-1947 June, Compact disc (Disc 12)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Heber C Kimball, Funny Paper Part II, 1947 June 27 (Track 40)
    - Heart Throbs of the West "Pioneer Mothers", Sim's Hat Spots (Can't record), 1947 May 9; 1947 May 15 (Track 41)
    - KDYL Days of '47 – Alta Dayton – Air-Check (Incomplete Recording), Veteran's Advisor, 1945 June 30 (Track 42)
    - Warriors of Peace Part One (Couldn't Record), Heart Throbs of the West "He Unknowing by Spoke the Truck" (?), 1946 April 21 (Track 43)
  - 1946 March-1946 June, Compact disc (Disc 13)
    - Warriors of Peace Part One (Couldn't Record), Heart Throbs of the West "He Unknowing by Spoke the Truck" (?), 1946 April 21 (Track 43)
    - Heart Throbs of the West "The Journey" Unnamed, 1946 March 17 (Track 44)
    - Heart Throbs of the West - Beaston Lewis Pied Piper of the Pioneers, 1946 June 16 (Track 45)
  - 1946 March-1948 August, Compact disc (Disc 14)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Stage Coach Romance Unnamed, 1946 April 7 (Track 46)
    - Heartthrobs of the West – Joshua Jerry, Warriors of Peace Part Two, 1946 March 3; 1946 March 31 (Track 47)
    - Children's Friend – Frontier Detective Unnamed, 1948 August 21 (Track 48)
  - 1948 July-1948 September, Compact disc (Disc 15)
    - Children's Friend – Frontier Detective Unnamed, 1948 August 21 (Track 48)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "The Dutch Doll", Children's Friend – Prairie Friends, 1948 July 31; 1948 July 24 (Track 49)
    - Children's Friend – Mysterious Beginnings – Red 6, Children's Friend of the Air – Rescue From the Rooftop, 1948 September 4; 1948 August 28 (Track 50)
  - 1947 February-1950 March, Compact disc (Disc 16)
    - Children's Friend – Mysterious Beginnings – Red 6, Children's Friend of the Air – Rescue From the Rooftop, 1948 September 4; 1948 August 28 (Track 50)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Mollie's Mistake", Children's Friend of the Air "Queenie Wanted to Dance", 1947 February 8; 1947 September 6 (Track 51)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – The Legend of the Snow Shoes, Carson, 1950 March 4; 1950 March 3 (Track 52)
  - 1947 February-1950 March, Compact disc (Disc 17)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – The Stowaway, Kaltenborn, 1950 March 11; 1950 March 10 (Track 53)
    - Children's Friend "Bucky" (Mt. Goat Story), Children's Friend – A Gift for Mr. Lincoln, 1950 February 18; 1950 February 11 (Track 54)
    - Children's Friend "Pedree Keeps A Promise", Miles (Couldn't Finish Recording due to damage), 1950 January 7, undated (Track 55)
  - 1947 April-1959 March, Compact disc (Disc 18)
    - Children's Friend "Pedree Keeps A Promise", Miles (Couldn't Finish Recording due to damage), 1950 January 7, undated (Track 55)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Eric's Library", Children's Friend "Dawn Boy", 1947 April 19; 1947 April 26 (Track 56)
    - PTA Youth Talks it Over Secret Society You and Your PTA Youth Talk it Over, 1959 March; 1952 April 2 (Track 57)
    - You and Your PTA, You and Your PTA, 1952 January 30; 1952 February 6 (Track 58)
  - 1951 January-1952 February, Compact disc (Disc 19)
    - You and Your PTA, You and Your PTA, 1952 January 30; 1952 February 6 (Track 58)
    - You and Your PTA, 1952 January 23 (Track 59)
    - You and Your PTA, Your P.T.A., 1952 January 16; 1951 January 1 (Track 60)
    - Your P.T.A. – Teenage Drivers, This is Your P.T.A. – Drama on Scholarships, 1951 January 22; 1951 January 30 (Track 61)
  - 1951 January-1952 January, Compact disc (Disc 20)
    - Your P.T.A. – Teenage Drivers, This is Your P.T.A. – Drama on Scholarships, 1951 January 22; 1951 January 30 (Track 61)
    - You and Your PTA, For Will Wright, 1952 January 2, undated (Track 62)
    - You and Your PTA, For Will Wright, 1952 January 2, undated (Track 63)
    - This is Your PTA – Panel, Unnamed, 1951 March 6, undated (Track 64)
  - 1947 February-1951 December, Compact disc (Disc 21)
    - This is Your PTA – Panel, Unnamed, 1951 March 6, undated (Track 64)
    - You and Your PTA (Can't Record), Unnamed, 1951 December 19, undated (Track 65)
    - This is Your PTA "Make Lloyd Principal", You and Your PTA "Sofe Says" KDYL, 1951 March 13; 1951 December 5 (Track 66)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Ben Alis Camel, Children's Friend – Jonathan and the School Wood Pile, 1947 February 15; 1947 February 1 (Track 67)
  - 1947 February-1947 April, Compact disc (Disc 22)
    - Heartthrobs of the West "The Tabernacle Organ", 4 Out (Can't Record), 1947 April 18, undated (Track 68)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – The Mississippi Saints, Utah Symphony Pre-Vue, 1947 February 7; 1947 February 6 (Track 69)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Ships, Boats, and Chest of Pioneers, Heart Throbs of the West – Early Arts and Crafts of Utah, March 21; 1947 February 14 (Track 70)
  - 1946 June-1948 September February, Compact disc (Disc 23)
    - Children's Friend – Danger on the Hill Road, Safe with Manuel – Utah Home Safety – Plug at End, 1947 March 15; 1947 March 29 (Track 71)
    - Children's Friend – Quivering Quagmire, Holbo, 1948 September 11, undated (Track 72)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Fauna Skee Gee Village, Children's Friend – Cindy Cinnamon, 1946 June 27; 1946 August 10 (Track 73)
  - 1946 April-1949 December, Compact disc (Disc 24)
    - Heart Throbs of the West "The Dorion Woman" (Beginning Damaged), 1947 July 24 (Track 74)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – The Lone Cedar Tree 4/11/46 (Damaged), 1946 April 11 (Track 75)
    - Children's Friend – Santa's Late Letter – Kearn's Orphanage (Damaged), Vocal Kearn's Orphanage (Damaged), 1949 December 18; 1947 December 18 (Track 76)
    - Children's Friend – Animals Speak Their Minds, Children's Friend "Bay of the Wagon Trails", 1949 July 30; 1949 July 23 (Track 77)
  - 1941 November-1951 April, Compact disc (Disc 25)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "The Wood Carver", Children's Friend of the Air – Trumbo the Elephant, 1949 September 17; 1949 September 10 (Track 78)
    - Children's Friend, Part 1 Xmas Lighting, 1941 November 29; 1947 November 28 (Track 79)
    - P.T.A. "Modern Methods of Teaching in the Primary Grades", Miles, 1951 April 1-24; 1951 April 23 (Track 80)
  - 1946 June-1951 April, Compact disc (Disc 26)
    - P.T.A. "Modern Methods of Teaching in the Primary Grades", Miles, 1951 April 1-24; 1951 April 23 (Track 80)
    - Children's Friend – The Baker Boy (End Damaged), Children's Friend – The Down of Peace, 1947 October 4; 1947 September 27 (Track 81)
    - Air Check 2 (End Damaged), Heart Throbs of the West – The Hand Car (End Damaged), 1946 June 22; 1946 June 21 (Track 82)
    - Children's Friend - Cat of Jack Barnegat – Buddy Binning (Damaged), 1947 June 21 (Track 83)
    - Children's Friend – Midsummer Snow Storm (Damaged), 1947 January 10 (Track 84)
  - 1946 May-1947 August, Compact disc (Disc 27)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Fort Douglas, Undated (Track 85)
    - Heart Throbs – Cent. Spot DUBS (Damaged), Pioneers (Damaged), Undated; 1947 June 9 (Track 86)
    - Children's Friend of the Sky "Little Pigs", 1947 August 7 (Track 87)
    - Part I "The Profet Jos. Smith" by Dr. Franklin West – Talk for Sunday Evening Church Radio Program, Part I "The Glory of God is Intelligence" by Dr. Franklin West – Talk for Sunday Evening Church Radio Programs (Skips Bad), 1946 May 19; 1946 May 26 (Track 88)
    - Part II "The Glory of God is Intelligence" by Dr. Franklin West – Talk for Sunday Evening Church Radio Program, Part II "The Prophet Jos. Smith" by Dr. Franklin West – Talk for Sunday Evening Church Radio Program (Skips), 1946 May 26; 1946 May 19 (Track 89)
    - Masterworks of Music – Lotte Lehmann, Program No. 7 Part 1, Undated (Track 90)
    - Masterworks of Music – Lotte Lehmann, Program No. 8 Part 1, Undated (Track 91)
  - 1947 February-1948 March, Compact disc (Disc 28)
    - Masterworks of Music – Lotte Lehmann, Program No. 1 Part 2, Undated (Track 92)
    - Masterworks of Music – Lotte Lehmann, Program No. 9 Part 1, Undated (Track 93)
    - Masterworks of Music – Lotte Lehmann, Program No. 9 Part 2, 1947 August 7 (Track 94)
    - Masterworks of Music – Lotte Lehmann, Program No. 10, Undated (Track 95)
    - Rep. Dawson – "Report From Congress", 1948 March 9 (Track 96)
    - WCBS – Talk y Mrs. WM. Stevenson, 1947 February 10 (Track 97)
    - NBC Radio – Digger O'Dell Speaks For Farm Safety NBC Radio – "National Farm Safety Week", Undated (Track 98)
  - 1947 April-1947 December, Compact disc (Disc 29)
    - NBC Radio – Digger O'Dell Speaks For Farm Safety NBC Radio – "National Farm Safety Week", Undated (Track 98)
    - KSL - Freedom Train Program Part II KSL - Christmas Guest Part II, 1947 December 23 (Track 99)
    - KSL – Dubbing – Lisle Bradford Chorus Part 2 KSL – Dubbing – Lisle Bradford Chorus Part 1, Undated (Track 100)
    - KSL – A Long Life + Merry One Part 3, KSL – A Long Life + Merry One Part 1, 1947 April 4 (Track 101)
  - 1947 March-1948 January, Compact disc (Disc 30)
    - KSL – A Long Life + Merry One Part 3, KSL – A Long Life + Merry One Part 1, 1947 April 4 (Track 101)
    - KSL – Youth and a Western Star Part I, KSL – Youth and a Western Star Part I, 1947 March 18; 1947 April 1 (Track 102)
    - Utah Symphony Orchestra Recorded from KSL Part 1, 1948 January 22 (Track 103)
  - 1948 February, Compact disc (Disc 31)
    - Utah State Symphony Orchestra Recorded from KSL Part 2, Utah State Symphony Orchestra Recorded from KSL Part 4, 1948 February 19 (Track 104)
    - Unknown Name – Labels Missing, Undated (Track 105)
    - Nab Lang-Worth – Bertrand Hirsch and His Magic Violin, Nab Lang-Worth – Golden Melodies Series, Undated (Track 106)
  - 1947 January-1947 January, Compact disc (Disc 32)
    - Nab Lang-Worth – Bertrand Hirsch and His Magic Violin, Nab Lang-Worth – Golden Melodies Series, Undated (Track 106)
    - Congressman Dawson, 1947 January 31 (Track 107)
    - Dewey Political Ads, Undated (Track 108)
    - KSL – One World Flight Part I, 1947 January 14 (Track 109)
    - KSL – One World Flight Part II, 1947 January 14 (Track 110)
  - 1946 July-1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 33)
    - KSL – Kendrick Johnson Dubbing From Koh Records (2 Skips Bad), 1946 July 5 (Track 111)
    - Youth and a Western Star Part II, 1947 April 15 (Track 112)
    - 2 4, 6, 1948 June 18 (Track 113)
  - 1944 September-1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 34)
    - KSL - R.L. 1, 1948 June 16 (Track 114)
    - KSL – Church of the Air Part I, 1946 January 6 (Track 115)
    - Democratic State Comm., 1944 September 28 (Track 116)
    - Orthacoustic Radio Recording – Collin Driggs at the Hammond Novachord Program No. 1, Orthacoustic Radio Recording – Collin Driggs at the Hammond Novachord Program No. 2, Undated (Track 117)
  - 1942-1948 February, Compact disc (Disc 35)
    - United States Recording Co. "Gov. Thomas E. Dewey", 1944 October 3 (Track 118)
    - Nab-Long-Worth – Lang-Worth Swing Orchestra Estelle Fields, Vocalist Nab- Long-Worth – Fanfares-Openings-Closings and Specialties Brass Band Selections (Too Damaged to Play), Undated (Track 119)
    - 121 Fl. Den Camp(?), 1942 (Track 120)
    - Congressman Dawson – Running Time 13'20", 1947 May 1 (Track 121)
    - Utah State Symphony Recorded from KSL Part 3, Utah State Symphony Recorded from KSL Part 1, 1948 February 19 (Track 122)
  - 1941 September-1947 June, Compact disc (Disc 36)
    - Lang-Worth – Jack Shaindlin and his Symphonic Band 1139, Lang-Worth – Szath-Myri and his Orchestra 1140, Undated (Track 123)
    - Political Talk – Senator E.Y. Robertson, 1944 October 14 (Track 124)
    - KSL - Senator McCarren Running Time 12'40", 1947 June 10 (Track 125)
    - Political Campaign Speech of Pres. Roosevelt – Part IV of IV, Undated (Track 126)
    - KSL – "Proudly We Hail" Cut from C.B.S. Part I, KSL - Budapest Stings for Sunday Midnight Station Break at End, 1941 September 26; 1941 September 29 (Track 127)
  - 1946 February-1947 April, Compact disc (Disc 37)
    - KSL - 1348 Infantile Paralysis Program Part 2, KSL - 1350 Infantile Paralysis Program Part 4, 1946 February 13 (Track 128)
    - KSL – Infantile Paralysis Program Pt. 8, KSL – Infantile Paralysis Program Pt. 6, 1946 February 13 (Track 129)
    - KSL - 4496 Granite High School Part 2, KSL - 4552 "Songs of Harry Clark" KSL Orchestra No. 1 – Harry Clark No. 2, 1947 March 26; 1947 April 2 (Track 130)
  - 1947 January-1947 March, Compact disc (Disc 38)
    - KSL - 4019 Budget Message of Gov. Maw Part 3, KSL - 4017 Budget Message of Gov. Maw Part 1, 1947 January 22 (Track 131)
    - KSL - 4370 Utah State Symphony Part III (Skips), KSL - 4368 Utah State Symphony Part II, 1947 March 5 (Track 132)
    - KSL - 4018 Budget Message of Gov. Maw Part 2, KSL - 4020 Budget Message of Gov. Maw Part 4, 1947 January 22; 1947 January (Track 133)
  - 1946 June, Compact disc (Disc 39)
    - Columbia – Masterworks of Music – Lotte Lehmann, Program No. 5 Part 1, Undated (Track 134)
    - Columbia – Masterworks of Music – Lotte Lehmann, Program No. 8 Part 2, Undated (Track 135)
    - KSL - 2377 Republican Convention Part III (Skips), KSL - 2373 Republican Convention Part I (Skips), 1946 June 1 (Track 136)
    - KSL - 2374 Republican Convention Part II (Skips), KSL - 2378 Republican Convention Part IV, 1946 June 1 (Track 137)
    - 12 Aunt Jenny, Undated (Track 138)
  - 1946 July, 1947 December; Compact disc (Disc 40)
    - 12 Aunt Jenny, Undated (Track 138)
    - Political – Stringham, Undated (Track 139)
    - Geo W. Malone 3, Geo W. Malone 2, 1946 July 30 (Track 140)
    - KSL - 2750 B.Y.U. Part 2, KSL - 2752 B.Y.U. Part IV, 1946 July 15 (Track 141)
    - KSL - 7071 Christmas Guest Part I, KSL - 8048 Freedom Train Program Part One, 1947 December 23, undated (Track 142)
  - 1946 January-1947 December, Compact disc (Disc 41)
    - KSL - 7071 Christmas Guest Part I, KSL - 8048 Freedom Train Program Part One, 1947 December 23, undated (Track 142)
    - KSL - 1 Gov Wilson 2 C.T. Bailey 3 George W. Raid 4 Tracy R. Welling 6 Deer Heuit Reed 7 Sanford, KSL - 927 Special Interview with Mr. Coray to be used on KSL Player Cut 2 (Can't Record), Undated; 1946 January 2 (Track 143)
    - KSL – Infantile Paralysis Program Parts VI and VIII, 1946 February 13 (Track 144)
    - KSL - 2806 Church of the Air Part 2, 1946 July 21 (Track 145)
    - KSL - 3874 Church of the Air Part II, 1946 January 5 (Track 146)
  - 1946 August-1947 April, Compact disc (Disc 42)
    - Nab-Lang-Worth - 986 Del Courtney and His "Candid Camera Music" Vocalists: Jack Milton-Earl Randall, Nab-Lang-Worth - 985 Jan Garber and His Orchestra Vocalist: Bob Davis, Undated (Track 147)
    - KSL - 4443 Youth and a Western Star Part II, KSL - 4544 Youth and a Western Star Part II, 1947 March 18; 1947 April 1 (Track 148)
    - No Labels, Undated (Track 149)
    - KSL - 306 Bates Boys Short, 1946 August 30 (Track 150)
  - 1946 May-1947 December, Compact disc (Disc 43)
    - Political Campaign Speech of President Roosevelt – Part III of IV, Undated (Track 151)
    - Political Campaign Speech of President Roosevelt – Part I of IV, Undated (Track 152)
    - KSL - 2219 Dr. West Talk For L.D.S. Sunday Evening Service Broadcast 9:00PM, 1946 May 12 (Track 153)
    - KSL - 6871 Princess of Mu, KSL – The Saint D-5 from CBS, 1947 December 3, undated (Track 154)
    - KSL - 2805 Church of the Air Part I, 1946 July 21 (Track 155)
  - 1941 June 15-1946 August, Compact disc (Disc 44)
    - KSL – Played by R.L., 1941 June 15 (Track 156)
    - Political Gov. W. Malone, 1946 August 12 (Track 157)
    - 9A The Fighting Senator Jeff Tyler – Richard Coogan, 7A Music, Undated (Track 158)
    - Nab-Lang-Worth - 746 Lang-Worth Military Band (First Track Missing Due to broken Vinyl), Nab-Lang-Worth - 745 Evalyn Tyner and Her Orchestra (First Track Missing Due to broken Vinyl), Undated (Track 159)
  - Undated, Compact disc (Disc 45)
    - Nab-Lang-Worth - 746 Lang-Worth Military Band (First Track Missing Due to broken Vinyl), Nab-Lang-Worth - 745 Evalyn Tyner and Her Orchestra (First Track Missing Due to broken Vinyl), Undated (Track 159)
    - Election Results Roosevelt – Dewey 1944, Undated (Track 160)
    - 16A 1944 Election Results, 13 Roosevelt – Dewey Election Results, Undated (Track 161)
  - 1941 June 15-1946 August, Compact disc (Disc 46)
    - KSL - 660B Lord Hallifax cut from CBS Part IV, KSL - 661A Lord Hallifax Address cut from CBS Part II, 1941 March 25; 1941 March 24 (Track 162)